HARMONY TREVENA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am a continuously curious fullstack software developer passionate about working in teams and finding creative solutions to technical problems. My previous experience as an operations and project management professional has me perfectly positioned to bridge the gap between development teams, designers and operations.



PROJECTS

Taskwork September 2020

Built with: HTML | CSS | Node | Express | Postgres View Here: Live | Github

A user-friendly project management tool that utilizes the scrum framework, allowing users to track project tasks, review those in flight and boost team efficiency.

- > Project managed a team of 3 junior developers utilizing the scrum framework.
- > Responsible for front-end development, mobile-first fully responsive UI/UX, brand creation and logo design.

To-Do Today August 2020

Built with: HTML | CSS | Javascript | JSON View Here: Live | Github

To-Do Today provides information about local events, in select cities, that are happening Today! Users can browse information about weather, concerts, festivals, sporting events, breweries and more.

- > Responsible for brand development, graphic design, UI/UX, customization and implementation of the Bulma Responsive Framework.
- > Collaborated with 3 colleagues from initial idea to deployment using the Agile methodology managed through GitHub Project.

Sean vs Al July 2020

Built with: Python3 | Pygame View Here: Demo | Github

Sean vs AI is a fully interactive puzzle game built in Python using Pygame. The goal is to solve coding problems that would be familiar to an entry-level developer.

- > Contributed player animation built using Pygame methods, game-board design and implementation, and quality control testing.
- > Developed in a team using GitHub, multiple branches and resolving merge conflicts.

EXPERIENCE

DigitalCrafts Atlanta, GA, USA

Manager of University & Strategic Partnerships

May 2020 - June 2020

Developed an end-to-end implementation process to successfully launch partnerships with universities, educational providers and strategic partners. Found and secured new partnership opportunities to grow business and nurtured relationships through implementation. Coordinated logistics, operations, marketing, and allocation of internal resources.

- > Created and launched partnership implementation process and managed crossorganizational collaboration.
- > Supported 3 university partners in launching and implementing a co-branded coding bootcamp.
- > Implemented and managed partnership specific landing pages, third party customer review accounts, organic marketing content and customer communication.

DigitalCrafts Atlanta, GA, USA

Operations Manager

January 2020 - May 2020

Launched pilot program in partnership with Kennesaw State University, College of Professional Education. Oversaw co-branded coding bootcamp partnership and implementation, daily campus operations and entire CRM process. Created content and provided marketing guidelines with the goal of finding and converting customers. Recruited, hired and onboarded Senior Level Software Engineers as instructors.

- > Managed customer pipeline from initial inquiry through enrollment.
- > Secured federal funding for customer tuition support to increase enrollment.
- > Launched marketing initiatives with industry organizations to grow customer base and increase enrollment.

Dixon Rye Atlanta, GA, USA

Project Manager

January 2018 – January 2020

Atlanta, GA, USA

Developed detailed work plans to efficiently and accurately complete projects. Coordinated logistics, purchases, installations, budgets and allocation of internal resources. Drove project performance KPIs using project management software in conjunction with team and client feedback. Managed project profitability and client/vendor payments.

- > Contributed to 20 projects with an average team size of 15.
- > Managed the largest revenue project to date, coming in under budget.

EDUCATION

DigitalCrafts Remote

Fullstack Immersive Software Development Bootcamp July 2020 - Present

Savannah College of Art and Design

Bachelor of the Fine Arts: Summa Cum Laude - 4.0 GPA Class of May 2017

harmonytrevena@gmail.com | harmonytrevena.com